Mss.B.St65p
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Tocantins, Leandro M., 1940, 1957
  - Todorovic, Mirjana, 1958
  - Tokumaru, Tadasu, 1962
  - Toll, Herman, 1966
  - Tomlinson, Willard, 1941-1942
  - Tompkins, Pendleton, 1967-1971
  - Tongudai, Subharee, 1966
  - Toomey, John A., 1943-1948
  - Topping, Norman, 1951-1966
  - Toral, Julio, 1949
  - Torbert, John Vernon, 1952
  - Toriello, Jose Lionel, 1951
  - Tornay, Anthony S., 1967
  - Torrano, Editha F., 1954
  - Torre, Joaquin Arturo de la, 1947-1969
  - Torres, Francisco E., 1951-1955
  - Townsend, Edward H., Jr., 1962-1964
  - Townsend, Mrs. John W., Jr., 1943
  - Townsend, Mrs. Leland C., 1947
  - Townsend, Murphy Furman, Jr., 1961
  - Townsend, Virginia, 1965
  - Tracy, F. Erwin, 1949
  - Tracy, Stephen E., 1940
  - Tramburg, John W., 1962
  - Trapp, Rupert von, 1940
  - Trask, Phyllis, 1938, 1970-1971
  - Traverso, Martha Alicia, 1956
  - Treblow Family, 1950
  - Treblow, I. Nathaniel, 1962-1965
  - Treffers, Henry P., 1952
  - Trey, Charles, 1967
  - Trimble, Mrs. Ralph, 1948
  - Trotter, Elizabeth, 1965
  - Troup, Roger C., 1951
  - Trower-Holland Inc., 1966
  - Troy, J.M., 1952
  - Truitt, R. Marshall, 1946-1965
  - Trumbore, Joan L., 1945
  - Trumbull, Merlin L., 1952
  - Trumper, John, 1962-1964
  - Ts'vi, Charlotte Chih-Hwa, 1948
  - Tucker, Cecil M., 1953-1955
  - Tucker, Samuel, 1962-1966
  - Tucker, William B., 1959
  - Tudor, Richard B., 1955
  - Tumay, Sezai Bedreddin, 1960
  - Tugendreich, Gustav, 1939-1942
  - Tullis, James L., 1955-1963
  - Tumen, Henry J., 1964
  - Tumulty, Philip A., 1954
  - Turel, Stanley E., 1962
  - Turino, Gerard M., 1952-1953
  - Turkman, Wahdeddin T., 1958, 1962
  - Turman, Christopher M., 1956
  - Turner, Evan H., 1964-1966
  - Turner, J.A., 1948
  - Turner, Thomas B., 1952
  - Tuttle, Russell C., 1962
  - Twaddell, Donald N., 1946-1947
  - Twaddle, Andrew C., 1970
  - Twiggar, Edward V., II, 1962
  - Tyler, Charles O., 1948-1959
  - Tyler, Norman A., 1956
  - Tyson, John T., 1960
  - Tyson, Katharine S., 1948
  - Tyson, Ralph M., 1941-1946
  - Tyson, Robert G., 1949
  - Tytel, Holly, 1970
  - Tzou, Y.F, 1947
  - Udandi, P.M., 1952-1967
  - Ufford Family, 1946
  - Ulrich, Paul H., 1945
  - Union Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1958
  - United Fruit Company, 1937-1941
  - United States Trust Company of New York, 1967
  - University House, Philadelphia, 1941
  - Unker, Lillian, 1940
  - Unknown, 1936, 1961
  - Upjohn Company, 1947-1963; 2.0 folders
  - Uramatsu, Fuki, 1952
  - Urbach, Charles, 1939-1950
  - Urbach, Frederick, 1952
  - Urenson, Bertha, 1966
  - Urologic and Cutaneous Review, 1942
  - Usher, Martha and Robert, 1955-1965
  - Vahlquist, Bo, 1953-1962
  - Vail, Harry F., 1945-1950
  - Valeri, O. Malagussi, 1958
  - Valyasevi, Aree, 1968
  - Vance, Peter W., 1956-1966; 2.0 folders
  - Van Alen, James H., 1956
  - Van Alen, William L., 1954-1972
  - Van Creveld, S., 1958-1964
  - Vandegrift, Harvey N., 1946-1963
  - Van Gelderen, H.H., 1953
  - Vanguard School, 1965
  - Van Hulzen, Donald, 1966
  - Van Lennep, Florence L., 1940
  - Van Loghem, J.J., Jr., 1950-1951
  - Van Meter, Ralph H., 1969
  - Vann, Mary Alice, 1947
  - Vannicola, Mario, 1946
  - Van Ormoudt, Anny Tillema, 1955
  - Van Rooyen, C.E., 1950-1952
  - Van Steenwyk, E.A., 1949
  - Van Weele, Marinus, 1961
  - Vassalluzzo, Julio E., 1970
  - Vaughan, Victor, III, 1967-1971
  - Vaux, Norris W., 1947-1948
  - Veeder, Borden S., 1941-1961
  - Veeneklaas, G.M.H., 1959-1964
  - Veeraraghavan, P., 1953
  - Veghelyi, P.V., 1947-1959
  - Velarde, A. Acosta, 1951
  - Velasco, Jose Antonio, 1956
  - Veldee, M.V., 1952
  - Velkoff, Cyril L., 1958
  - Venerable, James T., 1953-1962
  - Venhofen, Elisabeth, 1951
  - Verabutr, Yudhanindr, 1957-1958
  - Verdonk, Gaston, 1946-1957
  - Verlin, Jerome J., 1958
  - Veronesi, Ricardo, 1955-1962
  - Vesin, Paul, 1958
  - Vest, Walter E., 1955
  - Veterinary Students, 1964
  - Videbaek, Aa., 1956-1957
  - Vieuchange, Jean, 1949
  - Vignec, Alfred J., 1942-1951
  - Villamizar, Ramon Buenaver, 1955
  - Vinck, William G., 1971
  - Vining, Elizabeth, 1963
  - Viollier, G., 1952
  - Virginia, 1948
  - Virginia Medical Monthly, 1954
  - Vishnevsky, Aleksander Aleksandrovitch, 1952, 1958
  - Vodev, Eugene D., 1966
  - Vogel, Edward H., 1946
  - Vogt, Agnes R.B., 1939, 1948
  - Volunteers for Leader, 1954
  - Von Creveld, S., 1947
  - Von Laue, Hildegarde H., 1948
  - Von Magnus, Preben, 1970-1971
  - Von Schuching, Susanne, 1957
  - Vox Sanguinis, 1956-1964
  - Vulliamy, D.G., 1953
  - Waalkes, T. Phillip, 1959
  - Wada, Sunao, 1964
  - Wade, George R., 1949-1960
  - Waggener, James A., 1952
  - Wagner, Bernard M., 1955-1960
  - Wagner, Tobias, 1960-1961
  - Waife, S.O., 1952
  - Wainer, M. Robert, Jr., Undated
  - Waksman, Selman A., 1951
  - Walcher, Dwain N., 1950-1963
  - Walcott, George, 1961
  - Waldo, Frank B., 1952
  - Waldorf-Astoria, 1939
  - Walke, John T., 1946-1949
  - Walker, Arthur M., 1949-1953
  - Walker, Bruce E., 1959
  - Walker, Ethel, 1940
  - Walker, Graham McKelvy, 1948
  - Walker, James, 1947
  - Walker, Lillie Cutlar, 1944-1966
  - Walker, Peter, 1949
  - Walker, Mrs. Walter W., 1961
  - Wall, Robert L., 1969
  - Wallace, Albert J., 1942-1945
  - Wallace, Althea, 1961
  - Wallace, William M., 1948-1955
  - Wallach, Robert T., 1952
  - Waller, Ruth R., 1941
  - Waller, Shani, 1971
  - Wallerstein, L., 1963
  - Wallgren, Arvid, 1953-1960
  - Walling, R.K., 1948
  - Wallis, Allan D., 1944
  - Walrath, Florence D., 1940-1942
  - Walsh, John K.I., 1951
  - Walsh, R.J., 1948-1953
  - Walter, Carl W., 1953
  - Walters, Dorothy Davis, 1947-1950
  - Walton, Angela, 1950
  - Walton, Clarence H., 1950
  - Walton, George A., 1954
  - Walton, R. Lee, 1951
  - Waltz, Arthur D., 1941-1948
  - Waly, H. Gamil, 1951
  - Wanelik, Marion R., 1947
  - Wang, Catherine, 1960
  - Waples, Douglas, 1940
  - Ward, George, 1954-1955
  - Ward, Louisa, 1959
  - Ward, Robert, 1951-1972
  - Waring, Bernard G., 1947-1958
  - Waring, Grace W., 1941, 1962
  - Warkany, Josef, 1948-1954
  - Warner, Robert, 1959
  - Warren, A.J., 1941-1944
  - Warren, Joel, 1962
  - Warren, Robert O.Y., 1939-1970
  - Warren, Shields, 1961
  - Warrick, Lyn, 1962
  - Wartman, William B., 1953-1958
  - Washburn, Alfred H., 1941-1955
  - Washington, John A., 1951-1955
  - Washington Institute of Medicine, 1945-1948
    Periodical
  - Waterhouse, Alice M., 1963
  - Waterlow, John, 1950-1959
  - Waterman, John H., 1945
  - Watkinson, Geoffrey, 1954
  - Watson, Cecil James, 1946-1959
  - Watson, E.H., 1948
  - Watson, Edwin R., 1948
  - Watson, George A., 1941
  - Watson, Sally, 1942
  - Watts, Arthur P., 1941
  - Watts, Samuel G., 1950
  - Watumull, Mrs. G.J., 1958
  - Waverly Press, 1942
  - WCAU-TV, 1959-1960
  - Weakley, Frank L., 1955
  - Wear, Lawrence, 1949
  - Wear, Roland F., 1969
  - Wearn, Joseph T., 1952, 1968
  - Weaver, Harry M., 1953
  - Weaver, Ruth H., 1940-1958
  - Weaver, W. Wallace, 1939
  - Webb, C.H., 1947
  - Webb, Jean, 1945
  - Webb, William, 1961
  - Weber, Henry M., 1959
  - Weber, Ione, 1957
  - Webster, Leslie T., 1939
  - Webster, O.H., 1962-1964
  - Wechsler, H., 1947
  - Weech, A. Ashley, 1940-1963
  - Weeks, Annabel, 1960, 1966
  - Weeks, Lewis E., 1966-1967
  - Wegman, Myron E., 1949-1971
  - Wehrle, Paul F., 1955-1958
  - Weibel, Robert E., 1956-1959
  - Weidman, Fred D., 1941
  - Weikel, Malcolm, 1960
  - Weil, Marvin, 1947
  - Weil, William B., Jr., 1950-1970
  - Weinberg, Maurice G., 1946
  - Weinerman, E. Richard, 1963
  - Weinstein, David, 1960
  - Weir, John M., 1968-1969
  - Weiss, Charles, 1942-1954
  - Weiss, Edward, 1946-1950
  - Weiss, Eva and Robin, 1972
  - Weisser, C. William, 1951
  - Weissinger, Elizabeth, 1946
  - Welker, Leon, 1958
  - Weller, Stanley D.V., 1955
  - Weller, Thomas H., 1956-1965
  - Welling, John A., 1953
  - Wells, Henry, 1971
  - Wells, Mildred Weeks, 1940-1950
  - Wells, P. Arthur, 1971
  - Wells, William Firth, 1937-1963; 3.0 folders
  - Welsh, John B., 1967
  - Welsh, Mary, 1965-1966
  - Welt, Louis G., 1961
  - Welty, Robert F., 1970
  - Wendel, Douglas, 1941
  - Wendell, James I. and Kathleen Kirk, 1948-1955
  - Wenner, Herbert A., 1950-1968
  - Wentz, Clarkson, 1947
  - Werner, Georges H., 1958
  - Werther, Raymond, 1942-1960
  - Wescott, Lloyd B., 1966-1971
  - Wesselhoeft, Conrad, 1945
  - West, Harry F., 1951-1968
  - West, Nelson, 1961
  - West, William Nelson, III, 1961
  - Western Savings Fund Society, 1955-1961
  - Weston, Barbara, 1965-1970
  - Weston, Shannon Nelson, 1963
  - Weston, William III, 1962
  - Westover, J. Huston, 1950-1954
  - Westphal, Milton C., Jr., 1955-1972
  - Westtown School, 1962-1965
  - Wetzel, Norman C., Undated
  - Weymuller, Charles A., 1940-1969
  - Wheatley, George M., 1941-1961
  - Whedon, G. Donald, 1968-1969
  - Wheeler, Alexander B., 1961-1971; 2.0 folders
  - Wheeler, James E., 1946-1960
  - Wheeler, John P., 1962
  - Wheeler, Ralph E., 1953
  - Whelan, George L., 1941-1945
  - Whelan, Howard J., 1939
  - Whipple, Allen O., 1956
  - Whipple, Deryle T., 1961
  - Whipple, Dorothy V., 1940-1967
  - Whipple, G.H., 1958
  - Whitall, W. Brinton, 1967-1968
  - White, Colin, 1968
  - White, Gilbert F., 1949-1972
  - White, Holman, 1941
  - White, Jeffrey S., 1967
  - White, Paul Dudley, 1962-1963
  - White, Thomas Raeburn, Jr., 1948-1963
  - Whitehall Shop, 1941
  - Whitehead, Edwin C., 1952
  - Whitlock, Coleman M., 1949-1955
  - Whitney, E. Arthur, 1959
  - Whitson, Ruth Elizabeth, 1948
  - Whittemore, Ruth, 1954
  - Whittier, John R., 1957
  - Who's Who, 1941-1971
  - Widener Memorial Public School, 1954
  - Widerman, Arnold, 1942
  - Widman, Mrs. R.P., 1948
  - Wiederhold, Louis, III, 1952
  - Wiener, ______, 1961
  - Wiener, Maria, 1945
  - Wiggins, Milton L., 1958
  - Wight, Byron, 1958
  - Wiginton, Dr., 1943
  - Wiktor, T.J., 1968
  - Wilansky, Douglas L., 1963
  - Wilbar, C.L., 1958-1962
  - Wilbur, Dwight, 1949, 1969
  - Wilbur, Jordan R., 1960
  - Wilder, Theodore S., 1931-1970
  - Wildman, G.A., 1940
  - Wilhelm, Agatha, 1951
  - Wilken-Jensen, Knud, 1957
  - Wilkinson, Andrew W., 1960
  - Willard, Cecilia, 1958
  - Willard, Helen, 1952
  - Willard, John H., 1949
  - Williams, Chester P., 1967
  - Williams, Howard, 1947-1948
  - Williams, Ira, Undated
  - Williams, J.H., 1967
  - Williams, J. Peter, 1958
  - Williams, John C., 1954
  - Williams, John G., 1959
  - Williams, John N., 1952
  - Williams, Margaret L., 1952-1961
  - Williams, Philip F., 1940
  - Williams, R. G., 1949
  - Williams, Stanley, 1939-1958
  - Williamson, Alexander J., 1941
  - Williamson, Ernest G., 1940-1948
  - Williamson, John W., 1962
  - Willingham, Richard B., 1954-1971
  - Willis, David P., 1969
  - Willits, Lydia, 1971
  - Willoughby, George, 1960
  - Wills, William Mintzer, 1946-1947
  - Willson, Leonora S., 1952
  - Wilmer, Barbara, 1956-1957
  - Wilmer, Harry B., 1933-1943
  - Wilmington Morning News, 1946
  - Wilmot, Benneville Dayton, Jr., 1960-1961
  - Wilmot Castle Company, 1956
  - Wilson, Charles, 1947
  - Wilson, D. Wright, 1940-1950
  - Wilson, Edward Peter, 1960
  - Wilson, Edwin B., 1942-1954
  - Wilson, Evelyn Bouden, 1958-1962
  - Wilson, Helene, 1965
  - Wilson, James L., 1940-1965
  - Wilson, John F., 1959
  - Wilson, Lucius R., 1941
  - Wilson, Reginald, 1950
  - Wineberg, Julius J., 1957
  - Winegrad, Albert I., 1968
  - Wingall, William H., Jr., 1964
  - Winger, Elmo, 1951
  - Winick, Myron J., 1956
  - Winkler, Marvin H., 1958
  - Winlock, George Lane, 1941-1948
  - Winnemore, Charlotte, 1959
  - Winnicka, Victoria, 1946-1964
  - Winsaar, J., 1947
  - Winston, Lee, 1946
  - Winter, Sherl J., 1957
  - Winters, Robert W., 1962-1967
  - Winthrop Chemical Company, 1946
  - Wintrobe, Maxwell M., 1958
  - Wirth, H., 1968-1969
  - Wisdom of Hall, 1971
  - Wise, Francis R., 1942
  - Wise, Robert I., 1965-1966
  - Wiseman, Richard D., 1961
  - Wishik, Samuel W., 1952-1958
  - Wiskott, A., 1949
  - Wissler, Robert W., 1966
  - Wister, Caspar, 1962
  - Witebsky, Ernest, 1968
  - Withrow, Bobbie, Undated
  - Witte, John J., 1968
  - Wittenberg, M. Morris, 1948
  - Witts, L.J., 1953
  - Witzleben, C.L., 1962
  - Wixom, Robert L., 1961
  - Wludyka, Dorothy A., 1962
  - Wohl, Elizabeth, 1965-1967
  - Woiski, J. Renato, 1946
  - Wolcott, Caroline R., 1955-1956
  - Wolf, Frederick S., 1959
  - Wolf, Stewart, 1952-1953
  - Wolfbein, Seymour L., 1969
  - Wolfe, Abner, Undated
  - Wolfe, Richard E., 1941
  - Wolferth, Charles C., 1942-1954
  - Wolff, George T., 1961
  - Wolff, Otto H., 1958
  - Wolff, Sheldon M., 1966
  - Wolfish, Martin G., 1952
  - Wolfson, Sorrell, 1969
  - Wolman, Basil, 1950
  - Wolman, Irving, 1929-1971; 6.0 folders
  - Wolpe, Leon Z., 1950
  - Wolverton, Charles A., 1954
  - Wood, Alexander C., 1948
  - Wood, Anne, Undated
  - Wood, Curtis, 1943-1955
  - Wood, David E., 1952-1955
  - Wood, Edward C., 1941
  - Wood, Edwin C., 1968
  - Wood, Francis C., 1947-1969
  - Wood, H. Curtis, Jr., 1954-1969
  - Wood, Howard Page, 1946-1954
  - Wood, Ian J., 1945-1956
  - Wood, J. Edwin, Jr., 1968-1971
  - Wood, J.K. Williams, 1941
  - Wood, Morris Wistar, 1940-1946
  - Wood, Patrick, 1961
  - Wood, Richard D., 1953-1971; 3.0 folders
  - Wood, W. Barry, 1954-1958
  - Wood, William H., 1954
  - Woodard, C.E., 1966
  - Woodruff, Allen, 1961
  - Woodruff, D. Stratton, Jr., 1964
  - Woods, James H., 1967
  - Woody, Norman C., 1961
  - Woollcott, Joan, 1965
  - Woolman, Henry N., 1941-1942
  - Woolston, Joseph, 1969-1970
  - Woolston, William J., 1964
  - Woolwine, H.L., 1964
  - Workman, William G., 1948-1962
  - World Wide Abstracts, 1962-1963
  - World Wide Medical News Service, 1962
  - Worrall, Mr. and Mrs. Douglas H., 1952
  - Worrell, Howard, 1941
  - Worth, C. Brooke, 1953
  - Worthy, Mrs. R.C., 1950
  - Wortman, Herbert McC., 1952-1955; 2.0 folders
  - Wozniak, V., 1954
  - Wriggins, Howard, 1965
  - Wright, Carroll S., 1957
  - Wright, Charlotte, 1966
  - Wright, Mrs. Edward N., 1941
  - Wright, Estelle M.B., 1941
  - Wright, F. Howell, 1947-1961
  - Wright, H.J., 1960
  - Wright, Irving S., 1946
  - Wright, Sam Martin, 1946-1947
  - Wright, Thomas H., Jr., 1965
  - Wright, W.S., 1953
  - Wroblewski, Felix, 1967
  - Wu, Jui-Ping, 1940
  - Wurzel, Harold A., 1961
  - Wyatt, Virginia, 1951
  - Wylie, H. Boyd, 1954
  - Wylie, Laurence W., 1957
  - Wyllie, W.G., 1948-1949
  - Wyngaarden, James, 1965
  - Yadav, Vasant, 1960-1961
  - Yahraes, Herbert, 1953
  - Yakovac, William C., 1959-1962
  - Yalaz, Kalbiye, 1961-1962
  - Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine, 1938-1944
    Trask Memorial Issue
  - Yamada, Dr., 1956
  - Yamazaki, James M., 1946-1960
  - Yanagi, Kintaro, 1950
  - Yang, Ay-Kiang, 1947-1950
  - Yannet, Herman, 1953-1954
  - Yanney, Rodolph Morcos, 1958-1960
  - Yarborough, Ralph, 1969
  - Yarnall, D. Robert, 1940-1941
  - Yarnall, James B., 1969
  - Yarnall, Richard A., 1965
  - Yarnall, Stanley E., 1956
  - Yaukey, Grace S., 1968
  - Yazitzis, Michael, 1960
  - Yeager, George C., 1942
  - Yeakel, Mrs. Robert, 1964
  - Year Book Publishers, 1951-1962
  - Yeoman, Elmer E., 1947
  - Yermish, Mrs. Paul, 1963
  - Yippo, Arvo, 1955-1957
  - Yolken, Harry, 1966
  - Yoshikawa, Richard T., 1954
  - Youmans, John B., 1941-1945
  - Young, Barton R., 1958
  - Young, Daniel, 1951
  - Young, Donald R., Jr., 1966
  - Young, Edward L., 1950-1955
  - Young, James K., 1970
  - Young, John G., 1939-1947
  - Young, Keith R., 1965
  - Young, Reuben B., Jr., 1968
  - Young, Richard H., 1949
  - Young, William Frederick, 1958-1961
  - Yousry, F.R., 1952-1953
  - Yu, Ping-shi, 1955
  - Yun, Duk Jin, 1957
  - Zak, Frederick G., 1953
  - Zatlin, Gabriel, 1963
  - Zee, Dora, 1948
  - Zee, Harvey N., 1952-1954
  - Zeichner, Abraham M., 1963
  - Zeisler, Erwin Paul, 1961
  - Zellat, Joseph, 1941
  - Zeppenick, Mrs. A., 1963
  - Zergiebel, Malin F., 1949
  - Zhdanov, Victor, 1960-1967
  - Zheutlin, Lionel, 1949
  - Ziai, Mohsen, 1962
  - Ziegler, James E., Jr., 1946
  - Ziegler, Joyce, 1953
  - Zieverink, Sara E., 1962
  - Zimmer, Cynthia, 1945-1946
  - Zimmerman, Kent A., 1940
  - Zinsser, Harry, 1965
  - Zintel, Harold A., 1940-1953
  - Zisserman, Julius, 1971
  - Zita, Carmen C., 1960
  - Zollinger, William K., 1940-1943
  - Zucker, Theodore F., 1941
  - Zuckerman, A.J., 1969-1971
  - Zuelzer, Wolf W., 1949-1950
  - Zuleger, Frank, 1949-1950
  - Zweiman, Burton, 1968-1969
- Series II. Organizations, Foundations, and Conferences
  - Agency for International Development, 1964
  - Allegheny Association for Maternal and Child Health, Undated
  - Ambulatory Pediatric Association, 1971
  - America-Italy Society of Philadelphia, 1958
  - American Academy of General Practice, 1961-1963
  - American Academy of Microbiology
  - American Academy of Pediatrics, 1931-1970; 13.0 folders
  - American Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1961-1971
  - American Association for Cleft Palate Rehabilitation, 1959
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1936, 1963-1965
  - American Association for the Study of Liver Diseases, 1954-1970
  - American Association of Immunologists, 1954
  - American Association of Poison Control Centers, 1960
  - American Association of the History of Medicine, 1939-1941
  - American Association of University Professors, 1956
  - American Board of Pediatrics, 1936-1948, 1954-1964
  - American Cancer Society, 1955-1965
  - American Child Guidance Foundation, 1960-1961
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1954-1956
  - American Clinical and Climatological Association, 1952
  - American College of Physicians, 1940-1946
  - American College of Preventive Medicine, 1971
  - American College of Surgeons, 1960
  - American Epidemiological Society, 1945
  - American Foundation, 1956
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1939-1970; 16.0 folders
    Examiners, 1954-1963.
  - American Friends Service Committee-Abortion, 1970-1972
  - American Friends Service Committee-Agricultural Marketing Administration, Undated
  - American Friends Service Committee-American Cyanamid Company, 1940
  - American Friends Service Committee-Burgess, Alexander M., 1942-1946
  - American Friends Service Committee-Camp of Vernet, Undated
  - American Friends Service Committee-Care of European Children, 1939-1940
  - American Friends Service Committee-Care of Refugee Children, 1940-1941
    United States Department of Labor, standards of medical care for European children
  - American Friends Service Committee-Civilian Public Service, 1945
  - American Friends Service Committee-Clark, Bronson, 1971-1972
  - American Friends Service Committee-Cleveland, Lorraine K., 1970-1972
  - American Friends Service Committee-Committee on Race Relations, 1949-1952
  - American Friends Service Committee-Community Relations Committee, 1952-1954
  - American Friends Service Committee-Conscientious Objectors, 1941-1942
  - American Friends Service Committee-East Africa trips, 1970
  - American Friends Service Committee-European Relief Committee, 1940-1942
  - American Friends Service Committee-Executive Committee of Foreign Service Section, 1940-1941
  - American Friends Service Committee-Family Planning, 1963-1972; 12.0 folders
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-China, 1941-1950
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Denmark, 1949
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Far East, 1947
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Food, 1940-1947
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-France, 1940-1942
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Germany, 1945-1948
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-India, 1945-1946
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Japan, 1945
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Palestine, 1949-1951
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Paraguay, 1949
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Portugal, 1943
  - American Friends Service Committee-Foreign Service-Mission to Russia, 1948
  - American Friends Service Committee-Frawley, Margaret, 1941-1943
  - American Friends Service Committee-Friends Medical Society, 1950-1951
  - American Friends Service Committee-Heroin, 1971
  - American Friends Service Committee-Human Relations Committee, Undated
  - American Friends Service Committee-International Service, 1964-1972, undated; 10.0 folders
  - American Friends Service Committee-Job Opportunities Sub-Committee, 1954
  - American Friends Service Committee-Medical Committee, 1940, 1942
  - American Friends Service Committee-Miscellaneous, 1970-1971
  - American Friends Service Committee-National Committee on Food for the Small Democracies, 1941
  - American Friends Service Committee-Office Diary, 1942-1943
  - American Friends Service Committee-Prisoners of War, 1940
  - American Friends Service Committee-Read, Charles, 1970-1972, undated
  - American Friends Service Committee-Refugee Section, 1940
  - American Friends Service Committee-Relief and Rehabilitation, 1941
  - American Friends Service Committee-Rich, John F., 1940-1942
  - American Friends Service Committee-Russian Trip, 1958, 1960
  - American Friends Service Committee-Southwest American Indian Program, 1953
  - American Friends Service Committee-University Professors in Exile, Undated
  - American Friends Service Committee-Urbach, Charles, 1943
  - American Friends Service Committee-Vail, James G., 1940-1944
  - American Friends Service Committee-War Manpower Commission, 1940
  - American Friends Service Committee-Who Shall Live?, 1970-1972
  - American Friends Service Committee-Wood, Louise, 1970
  - American Friends Service Committee-Yellow Fever Immunization, 1942
  - American Friends Service Committee-Young Friends Movement, 1947-1948
  - American Gastroenterological Association, 1962
  - American Gynocological Society, 1958-1959
  - American Heart Association, 1949-1955
  - American Hospital Association, 1957-1962
  - American Human Serum Association, 1938-1941
  - American Medical Association, 1932-1970; 7.0 folders
  - American Medical Association-Committee on Foods, Undated
    Vitamin D Milk.
  - American Medical Association-Council on Drugs, 1957-1958
  - American Medical Association-Council on Pharmacy and Chemistry, 1948-1954; 7.0 folders
  - American Medical Association-Journal, 1945-1959, 1970-1971; 3.0 folders
  - American Medical Association-Residency Review Committee for Pediatrics, 1967-1969, undated; 2.0 folders
  - American Medical Association-Scientific Program, 1957
  - American Medical Association-Television program, 1963
  - American Men of Medicine, 1959-1960
  - American Men of Science, Undated
  - American National Red Cross, 1942-1963; 2.0 folders
  - American Pediatric Society, 1932-1972, undated; 18.0 folders
  - American Pharmaceutical Association, 1955, 1963
  - American Philosophical Society, 1953-1972; 11.0 folders
  - American Philosophical Society-Black Coalition, 1969
  - American Philosophical Society-Daland Fellowship Committee, 1953-1971; 12.0 folders
  - American Philosophical Society-Grants and Fellowships, 1968
  - American Philosophical Society Wistar Association, 1967, 1969
  - American Public Health Association, 1932-1968
  - American Trudeau Society, 1950
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1960
  - Anatomy Committee, 1951
  - Annual Health Conference, 1953
  - Armed Forces Epidemiological Board, 1949-1958, 1971
  - Army Epidemiological Board, 1941-1953; 32.0 folders
  - Association des Pediatres de Langue Francaise, 1967
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1954
  - Association for Voluntary Sterilization, 1969
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1956-1964
  - Association of American Physicians, 1939-1970, undated; 2.0 folders
  - Association of Interns and Medical Students, 1949-1950
  - Association of Pediatricians of India, 1954